paidsurveysgroup.com 2010-06-12

# Paid Surveys Group

## Privacy Policy

Last modified: January 26, 2010

We recognize that privacy is important. This Privacy Policy applies to all of the products, services and websites offered by our company & this website as well as its subsidiaries or affiliated companies. 

#### Information we collect and how we use it

All our services require you to register for an account or provide personal information to us. In order to provide our full range of services, we may collect the following types of information: 

  * **Information you provide -** When you sign up for an Account that requires registration, we ask you for personal information (such as your name, email address and an account password). For some services, we also request credit card or other payment account information which we maintain in encrypted form on secure servers. We may combine the information you submit under your account with information from our other services or third parties in order to provide you with a better experience and to improve the quality of our services. 
  * **Cookies -** When you visit our websites, we send one or more cookies – a small file containing a string of characters – to your computer or other device that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service, including for storing user preferences, improving search results and ad selection, and tracking user trends, such as how people use our website. We may set one or more cookies in your browser when you visit our websites. 
  * **Log information -** When you access your account, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. 
  * **User communications -** When you send email or other communications to us or your customers, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. 
  * **Affiliated Services and partner sites -** We offer some of our services on or through other web sites. Personal information that you provide to those sites may be sent to us in order to deliver the service. We process such information under this Privacy Policy. The affiliated sites mention above may have different privacy practices and we encourage you to read their privacy policies. 
  * **Gadgets -** We may make available third party applications through its services. The information collected by us when you enable a gadget or other application is processed under this Privacy Policy. Information collected by the application or gadget provider is governed by their privacy policies. 
  * **Links -** We may present links in a format that enables us to keep track of whether these links have been followed. We use this information to improve the quality of our search technology, customized content and advertising. 
  * **Other sites -** This Privacy Policy applies to our services only. We do not exercise control over websites and applications, products or services, or links from within our various services & websites. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. 

Our company processes personal information on our servers in the United States of America and in other countries. In some cases, we process personal information on a server outside your own country. We may process personal information to provide our own services. In some cases, we may process personal information on behalf of and according to the instructions of a third party, such as our affiliated partners. 

#### Information sharing

There is no guarantee that we won’t share you basic contact details such as, but not limited to full name, email address and telephone number.

#### Information security

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data. 

We restrict access to personal information our employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. 

#### Data integrity

Our company processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Privacy Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy notice. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services or as otherwise permitted under this Policy. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary. 

#### Accessing and updating personal information

When you use our services, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate.We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing this type of request, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes), or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort. Some of our services have different procedures to access, correct or delete users’ personal information 

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and it is your responsibility to view this page and update yourself with any changes we might make. Each version of this Privacy Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its effective date.
